ASIF SYED

A Master's in Business Analytics & Data Science student at Oklahoma State University

https://linktr.ee/asifsyd | +1-405-894-2106 | asif.syed@okstate.edu

CAREER SUMMARY:

I am a current Master's student at Oklahoma State University, actively looking for summer internship opportunities to gain relevant industry experience in the data science & analytics fields. I actively create data science-related content on LinkedIn and my blog, and I have four years of work experience in a professional setup as an SAP consultant.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Deloitte Consulting, India

SAP Customer Service Consultant | Nov, 2021 - Jul, 2022

 Proactively identified and fixed issues with a healthcare sector client's automatic invoicing in its SAP ERP system. It ensured close to 95% success rate of invoice transmissions to this client's customers in the later months.

Infosys Limited, India

SAP Supply Chain Management Consultant | Jul, 2021 - Nov, 2021

 Assisted a global client in the consumer electronics sector by implementing a new order fulfillment method in its SAP ERP. Approximately 15% of new orders are being generated via this fulfillment method after this implementation

Accenture, India

SAP Master Data Analyst | May, 2018 - Jul, 2021

• Successfully automated the process of master data creation in SAP with the help of a VBA Macro in Excel for an American client that deals with the household cleaning supplies business. It saved at least 20 hours of manual effort per week for the Master Data Management team.

ACADEMIC PROJECTS:

Building a Natural Language Processing based recommender system.

I am part of a four-member team working to build a system that recommends the names of content-creators in various platforms to PR professionals based on the topics for an American telecommunications company

EDUCATION:

2022 - 2024 | Oklahoma State University, United States

Master's in Business Analytics & Data Science

2014-2018 | Chaitanya Bharathi Inst. of Tech, India

Bachelor's of Engineering in Civil Engineering

SKILLS:

Python, MySQL, Basics of Machine Learning, Tableau, and Microsoft Excel.